http://familyfed.org/privacy

FamilyFed.org Privacy Policy - FFWPU USA
HomeAbout UsWho We AreContact UsDirectoryPressroomResourcesJobsNewsHappenings Near & FarCommunity NewsTrue Parents’ MessagesInternational NewsShare a StorySubscribe to NewsletterTeachingsThe Divine PrincipleHoly ScripturesChosen WorkshopsDivine Principle WorkshopsGodibleStoreMinistriesBlessing & FamilyTribal MessiahshipYouth & Young AdultSeonghwaEventsDonateNational MinistryLocal CommunitiesNational Victory FundRallies of HopeSeonghwa AnniversaryManage My Donations Search
World peace needs you.Join the national conditionWorld peace needs you.Join the national condition
FamilyFed.org Privacy Policy
HSA UWC operates FamilyFed.org, DPLife.info, BFM.FamilyFed.org, BlessingAmerica.org, hjfamilyfest.org, PeaceKingCup.com and HSAbooks.com (hereinafter “website”).
Information Collection and Use
While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. Personal information includes, but is not limited to your name, address, and date of birth, occupation, education, and language. We may use your personal information to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services. From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices. We may also use your personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis and research.
Cookies and Other Technologies
The website may use “cookies” and other technologies to help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that IP addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.
You can disable “cookies” in your browser, however please note that certain features of our website will not be available once “cookies” are disabled.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
The website may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the webite. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Pressroom | Donate | Privacy Policy | Contact Us
Follow Us on Facebook and Instagram
481 8th Ave, New York, NY 10001
Official Website of Family Federation for World Peace and Unification USA
Copyright © 2020
FFWPU, USA. All Rights Reserved.
Pressroom | Donate | Privacy Policy
| My Account | About Us | Contact Us | National Council | Job Opportunities
Official Website of Family Federation for World Peace and Unification USA
Copyright © 2020 FFWPU. All Rights Reserved.
True ParentsBlessing & FamilyWeekly UpdateiPeace TVIn MemoriamDP LifeHappenings Near & FarThis Week in HistoryContact UsPressroom
